Guide to the Argus Book Shop Correspondence
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Restricted Fragile
  - Box 12, folder 423 (Box 18, Folder 696)
  - Box 12, folder 426 (Box 18, Folder 697)
  - Box 12, folder 428 (Box 18, Folder 698)
  - Box 12, folder 429 (Box 18, Folder 699)
  - Box 12, folder 431 (Box 18, Folder 700)
  - Box 12, folder 432 (Box 18, Folder 701)
  - Box 12, folder 433 (Box 18, Folder 702)
  - Box 12, folder 434 (Box 18, Folder 703)
  - Box 12, folder 436 (Box 18, Folder 704)
  - Box 12, folder 442 (Box 18, Folder 705)
  - Box 12, folder 444 (Box 18, Folder 706)
  - Box 13, folder 447 (Box 18, Folder 707)
  - Box 13, folder 448 (Box 18, Folder 708)
  - Box 13, folder 449 (Box 18, Folder 709)
  - Box 13, folder 456 (Box 18, Folder 710)
  - Box 13, folder 458 (Box 18, Folder 711)
  - Box 13, folder 461 (Box 18, Folder 712)
  - Box 13, folder 463 (Box 18, Folder 713)
  - Box 13, folder 464 (Box 18, Folder 714)
  - Box 13, folder 466 (Box 18, Folder 715)
  - Box 13, folder 467 (Box 18, Folder 716)